<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Star Wars - Fully Functional Lightsabers (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.StarWarsFullyFunctionalLightsabers</packageId>
  <author>Xen and Jecrell</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/StarWarsFullyFunctionalLightsabers</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>jecrell.jecstools</packageId>
      <displayName>JecsTools</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2195729899</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>jecrell.jecstools</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>Update of Xen and Jecrells mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=918200645

[img]https://i.imgur.com/wtwHAQu.png[/img]

Support-chat:
https://invite.gg/mlie

Non-steam version:
https://github.com/emipa606/StarWarsFullyFunctionalLightsabers
	
- This is an unofficial port
- This will be removed when/if Jecrell comes back

--- Original Description ---
Adds constructable full-SFX lightsabers that can activate, load crystals, and deflect bullets.

A16 - GitHub Branch -&gt; https://github.com/jecrell/Star-Wars---Fully-Functional-Lightsabers/tree/A16


::::: NOTICE :::::
::::: THIS MOD NOW REQUIRES JECSTOOLS FOR A17 ::::::
Download
http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=932008009

Thanks to
Jedi Master Ailan
for his direction and inspiration in the creation of this mod. Without his help and support this would have never happened.

Quick start notes:
Lightsabers can be constructed at the component assembly bench.
Crystals can be refined from rocks at the electric smelter.
Rare crystals can be found out in RimWorld for sale from merchants or at enemy bases.
Legendary crystals can be found similarly to artifacts as well as in the clutches of Star Wars faction leaders.

Reference
Lightsaber Recipe
-1x lightsaber casing
-1x lightsaber internals

Lightsaber casing
-15 plasteel
-5 components

Lightsaber internals
-25 plasteel
-15 steel
-5 components

Lightsaber crystals
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1poiSM7jAlEvDq5fuEsSNwszlSNGmNiW42sp8G3Ujp-Q/edit?usp=sharing

Technical Details Information
Lightsabers could be the most extensive C# coded weapons available in RimWorld.
Included on a lightsaber are the following C# libraries:
Extra sounds Component
Activatable visual effect component
Crystal slot loadable component
Oversized weapon component
Deflection and reflection component
Customized lightsaber C# library

Most of these elements can be used by other modders by relocating the assemblies to their own mod folder to make their own mods using these components. So if you'd like to make a gun with different kinds of loadable ammunition, or a different sort of laser sword, now is a good time.

Special thanks to all those that support me (and help me pay the rent) on Patreon (August 2017):
Jedi Master Ailan, Shane Malley, Dakota Pohlman, Falloutmonk, Slick Liquid, Thom Black ShotgunFace, Fredric Sundberg, Dan Winn, Toss Antilles, Sarah Banks, Undead Jackel, Michin, Chelsea, Caine Detueur, Yewty Oxman, Jerod Clayton, Arty Kubin, Ashleigh Miller, infinity421, TheDayDude, Jacob Duga, Ryan Brock, Evan Hwang, Moshat, Christopher, Don Butterblume, John Boehr, George Chong Chuang Ming, Oliver White, Helpful Bot, vincent de keijzer, roxxploxx, Legless, Christopher Abel, Karol Rybak, Mathias Broxvall, Mark, Tim Stillson, Lachlan Easton, Nemuri Hime, Sera, Christian Hermansen, NiNe Bottles of Rum, Populous25, Steven James, Marcus Siraenu, Michael Lauder, meatface.

Lightsaber Developers
Programming by Jecrell.
Assets and XML by Xen.
Logo/Art designed by Harrison Gaushell (Website[harrisongaushell.com])
Spanish translation by Bub.
French translation by MrFootman.
German translation by Lauri7x3</description>
</ModMetaData>